[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ひっこしします' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "引っ越します"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かよいます' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "通います"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'そば, がわ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "側"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ころ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "頃"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ことば' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "言葉"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せっとうじ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "接頭辞"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せつびじ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "接尾辞"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'だいがっこう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "大学校"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんじてんしゃ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "新自転車"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ふしんせつ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "不親切な"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ごじゅうしょ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "御住所"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けんきゅうじょ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "研究所"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'えいがかん' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "映画館"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おんがくか' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "音楽家"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'どうぶつえん' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "動物園"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'どうぶつ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "動物"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'えん' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "園"
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'としょかん' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "図書館"
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ふるほんや' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "古本屋"
    },
    {
        "id": "20",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんぶんしゃ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "新聞社"
    },
    {
        "id": "21",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ふゆうめい' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "不有名"
    },
    {
        "id": "22",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ごはん' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "御飯"
    },
    {
        "id": "23",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ふにんき' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "不人気"
    },
    {
        "id": "24",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんこうえん' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "新公園"
    },
    {
        "id": "25",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ぎんこうか' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "銀行家"
    },
    {
        "id": "26",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'さっか' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "作家"
    },
    {
        "id": "27",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんさくぶん' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "新作分"
    },
    {
        "id": "28",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ところ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "所"
    },
    {
        "id": "29",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せまくて, ちいさいところ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "狭くて、小さいところ"
    },
    {
        "id": "30",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'じゅうしょ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "住所"
    },
    {
        "id": "31",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'きんじょ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "近所"
    },
    {
        "id": "32",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'めいじょ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "名所"
    },
    {
        "id": "33",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とくべつなしごとすること' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "特別な仕事すること"
    },
    {
        "id": "34",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けんきゅうじょ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "研究所"
    },
    {
        "id": "35",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しやくしょ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "市役所"
    },
    {
        "id": "36",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けいむしょ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "刑務所"
    },
    {
        "id": "37",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ジョウ・ば' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "場"
    },
    {
        "id": "38",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ひとがあつまるところです' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "人が集まる所です"
    },
    {
        "id": "39",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かいじょう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "会場"
    },
    {
        "id": "40",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'よくじょう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "浴場"
    },
    {
        "id": "41",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'いちば' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "市場"
    },
    {
        "id": "42",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'なにかおこなうことです' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "何か行うことです"
    },
    {
        "id": "43",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'げきじょう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "劇場"
    },
    {
        "id": "44",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しきじょう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "式場"
    },
    {
        "id": "45",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せんじょう' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "戦場"
    },
    {
        "id": "46",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'く' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "区"
    },
    {
        "id": "47",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とちをわけたところ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "土地を分けたところ"
    },
    {
        "id": "48",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'がっく' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "学区"
    },
    {
        "id": "49",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とっく' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "特区"
    },
    {
        "id": "50",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんじゅくく' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "新宿区"
    },
    {
        "id": "51",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'チ・ジ' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "地"
    },
    {
        "id": "52",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ちめんやとち' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "地面や土地"
    },
    {
        "id": "53",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しゃくち' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "借地"
    },
    {
        "id": "54",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ぼち' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "墓地"
    },
    {
        "id": "55",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'さんち' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "山地"
    }
]